### **MILAN BARANDE**

Front end developer

milanbarande.com linkedin.com/in/milan-barande aithub.com/MilanBarande



75011 Paris, France milan.barande@gmail.com +33 6 31 27 24 31

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a front-end developer with over 4 years of experience. I care about UX, performances, code quality and accessibility. I enjoy teamwork and training junior developers. I'm currently looking for a front-end (or mobile)

mission in Paris and/or remotely.

I am open to part-time work.

# Node JS

React

**SKILLS** 



**JavaScript** 







Next JS



Redux



Freelance

Paris, France

Freelance

Paris, France

**Permanent** 

Paris, France

Freelance Paris, France

Permanent

Paris, France

contract

contract

**EDUCATION** 

2017 Le Wagon Full Stack web development

Le Wagon Montreal, Batch #77

2016-**Neuroscience** - Concordia University

2017 Research Assistant at the PERFORM Center

Sleep Lab

2016-**Neuroscience Microprogram** 2017 University of Montreal - Concordia U

2013-**Kinesiology Bachelor's** 

2016 University of Montreal

#### **EXPERIENCE**

DIOR

DIOR

01/2021 - 06/2022

08/2020 - 01/2021

04/2019 - 08/2020

12/2017 - 11/2019

Front end developer Parfums Christian Dior

Front end developer **Christian Dior Couture** 

Front end developer **Christian Dior Couture** 

Working on the front-end and GraphQL API of dior.com, an isomorphic app entirely written in functional programming and built with React, NextJS, TypeScript, Redux, ApolloGraphQL, recompose, rx-js...

### **Workshop Lead**

Le Wagon

Occasionaly leading coding workshops at Le Wagon such as:

- Creating a landing page with HTML and CSS

### 09/2017 - 04/2019

- Introduction to JavaScript

- Introduction to React

### Front end developer Bluenove

Developing Assembl, an Open Source application that enables thousands of people to work together effectively on the definition of new ideas. Assembl's frontend is built with React, Redux, GraphQL, Sass, Jest, flow, webpack

## **LANGUAGE**

**FRENCH** Mother tongue

**ENGLISH** 

Fluent

**GERMAN** 

Fluent

**PORTUGUESE** Intermediate

#### **HOBBY AND INTERESTS**















Sports Neuroscience











